[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2005 hit comedy was written, directed and produced by Judd Apatow, and starred Steve Carell, Seth Rogen and Paul Rudd.", "correct_answer": "The 40-Year-Old Virgin", "incorrect_answers": ["Kicking and Screaming", "Bruce Almighty", "Evan Almighty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What celebrated film director worked on the 1960 horror movie Psycho?", "correct_answer": "Alfred Hitchcock", "incorrect_answers": ["Stanley Kubrick", "Milos Forman", "Woody Allen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these coat colors is not found in wild Red Fox populations?", "correct_answer": "Black", "incorrect_answers": ["Golden", "Spotted", "Red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Black Sea, whose waters are known to be meromictic, is the largest water basin in the world where water layers do not intermix, and, thus, lack the dissolved form of what?", "correct_answer": "Oxygen", "incorrect_answers": ["Salt", "Nitrogen", "Hydrogen Sulfide"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character in the movie Casablanca was interrupted by Rick while singing, You must remember this / A kiss is still a kiss / A sigh is just a sigh ...?", "correct_answer": "Sam", "incorrect_answers": ["Ilsa", "Captain Renault", "Victor Laszlo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Margaret Mitchells only book written in 1936?", "correct_answer": "Gone With The Wind", "incorrect_answers": ["Death on the Nile", "Double Indemnity", "Inherit The Wind"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Between the 1920s and 1940s, the pink color was considered appropriate for this group of people, but later it became popular with others too.", "correct_answer": "Boys", "incorrect_answers": ["Babies", "Young women", "High-class people"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Malawi, Nigeria and Botswana, the official language is this.", "correct_answer": "English", "incorrect_answers": ["French", "Portuguese", "Spanish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The clavicle is the bone that connects your upper arm to the rest of your body via your shoulder. What is the clavicle more commonly known as?", "correct_answer": "the collar bone", "incorrect_answers": ["the shoulder bone", "the neck bone", "the shin bone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name used for young rabbits?", "correct_answer": "Kittens", "incorrect_answers": ["Fluffles", "Puppies", "Conies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Richard Chamberlain has portrayed Jason Bourne.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie, directed by Academy Award-winning director, Robert Zemeckis, includes the often quoted line Life was like a box of chocolates. You never know what youre gonna get.?", "correct_answer": "Forrest Gump", "incorrect_answers": ["The Polar Express", "What Lies Beneath", "Back to the Future"]}]